const questions = [
  {
    question: 'What was the name of the first submarine used for combat, which was during the U.S. Revolutionary War?',
    answers: [
      'Avenger',
      'Tortoise',
      'Ohlman',
      'Poseidon'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the names of the control surfaces on a submarine that assist in pitching the bow up or down to control depth?',
    answers: [
      'Depth planes',
      'Fins',
      'Diving planes',
      'Horizontal planes'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'During World War 2, submarines used the following for propulsion:',
    answers: [
      'Electric',
      'Nuclear',
      'Diesel',
      'Diesel on the surface and electric at depth'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the popular name of the sound that a submarine’s active sonar produces?',
    answers: [
      'Ping',
      'Echo',
      'Pong',
      'Tweet '     
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year did the U.S.S. Triton make the first submerged voyage around the world in 83 days?',
    answers: [
      '1950',
      '1960',
      '1970',
      '1980' 
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'Today’s nuclear submarines are called this because:',
    answers: [
      'They carry nuclear weapons',
      'The are powered by a nuclear reactor and they carry nuclear weapons',
      'Their structure mimics the nucleus of a cell',
      'They are powered by a nuclear reactor',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the name of the submarine that first reached the deepest part of the ocean near Guam?',
    answers: [
      'Nautilus',
      'Seeker',
      'Trieste',
      'Stolger'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'Submarines rely on these to control their buoyancy:',
    answers: [
      'Depth chambers',
      'Ballast tanks',
      'Air tanks',
      'Compression chambers'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'In 2000, the remains of the Hunley, the first marine to sink a ship were discovered off of the Carolina coast. What war did this submarine serve in?',
    answers: [
      'World War II',
      'Revolutionary War',
      'War of 1812',
      'Civil War'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'Today’s periscope rely on the following to guide the path of light:',
    answers: [
      'Prisms',
      'Mirrors',
      'Lenses',
      'Cameras'      
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }        
];